Guide to the Office of the President Records, Virginia B. Smith Files, 1950-2010 (bulk 1977-1986)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series IX. Additions
  - Christmas Cards (To Vassar Community), 1987 (Folder 31.20)
  - Ken Cool — Grants Information, 1985-1989 (Folder 31.21)
  - Hudson Greenway Coalition, 1988 (Folder 31.22)
  - Inauguration, 1986 (Folder 31.23)
  - FDF’s Inaugural Speech, 1986 (Folder 31.24)
  - VBS Memorandum, Jun 11, 1986 (Folder 31.25)
  - Inauguration (II), 1986 (Folder 31.26)
  - [Student] Appeal (Highly Confidential), 1989 (Folder 31.27)
  - NIH — Site Visit, 1985 (Folder 31.28)
  - [Student] Appeal (Confidential), 1989 (Folder 31.29)
  - Obscene Phone Calls, 1985 (Folder 31.30)
  - [Student] Appeal (Confidential), 1989 (Folder 31.31)
  - [Student] Appeal (Confidential), 1987 (Folder 31.32)
  - Retreat Renovations, 1987-1988 (Folder 31.33)
  - Requests/Information, 1985-1989 (Folder 31.34)
  - South Africa Ed Program, 1986 (Folder 31.35)
  - Suffrage, 1986 (Folder 31.36)
  - Conference of Academic Deans, Oct 25, 1985 (Folder 31.37)
  - [Name Removed] Lawsuit (Confidential), 1986 (Folder 31.38)
  - Student Advisees “A”, 1986 (Folder 31.39)
  - American Way/American Heart Association Campaign, 1986-1988 (Folder 31.40)
  - Title IX of Education Amendment of 1972 Violation, 1986 (Folder 31.41)
  - URSI Faculty Development Workshop, Jul 1986 (Folder 31.42)
  - Vassar Journal, 1984-1985 (Folder 31.43)
  - URSI, 1987-1989 (Folder 31.44)
  - URSI Mini symposium, Oct 1986 (Folder 31.45)
  - Vassar Brothers Hospital, 1987 (Folder 31.46)
  - Western Maryland College (Board of Trustees), 1986-1987 (Folder 31.47)
  - Tentative Dates of Board of Trustees Meetings, 1979-1980 (Folder 32.1)
  - Trustee Action on South Africa Investments, Nov 2, 1978; (1 folder) (Folder 32.2)
  - Terms of Office, 1979 (Folder 32.3)
  - Addresses — Board of Trustees, 1979-1980 (Folder 32.4)
  - Cambridge Associate’s Evaluation and Recommendations — The Administrative Structure at Vassar College, 1979 (Folder 32.5)
  - Chairman of the Board — Mary St. John Villard, 1979 (Folder 32.6)
  - Addresses and Telephone Numbers — Board of Trustees, 1979-1980 (Folder 32.7)
  - Committee Assignments — Board of Trustees, 1979-1980 (Folder 32.8)
  - Dates of Board Meetings, 1979-1980 (Folder 32.9)
  - Entertainment — Trustee-Faculty Entertainment (Folder 32.10)
  - AAVC Equipment Request, Oct 11, 1979 (Folder 32.11)
  - Art Department — Program of Space Requirements, 1979 (Folder 32.12)
  - Chemistry Laboratory — Current status of Planning: Progress Report, Oct 3, 1979 (Folder 32.13)
  - Early Retirement for Professors — Julia McGrew and Louis Pamplume, Oct 12, 1979 (Folder 32.14)
  - Middle States Association Report to Faculty, Administration, Trustees, Students, 1979 (Folder 32.15)
  - Proceedings Report — Board of Trustees Meeting, Oct 1979 (Folder 32.16)
  - Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Trustees, Oct 1979 (Folder 32.17)
  - Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Trustees — Executive Session, Oct 1979 (Folder 32.18)
  - Executive Committee Meeting, May 1979 (Folder 32.19)
  - Proceedings — Board of Trustees Meeting, May 1979 (Folder 32.20)
  - Trustees, 1980 (Folder 32.21)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Oct 1979 (Folder 32.22)
  - Audit Committee — Board of Trustees, 1979-1980 (Folder 32.23)
  - Budget Committee — Board of Trustees, 1979-1980 (Folder 32.24)
  - Building and Grounds Committee — Board of Trustees, 1979-1980 (Folder 32.25)
  - CICU Correspondence Committee — Board of Trustees, 1979 (Folder 32.26)
  - Development Committee — Board of Trustees, 1979 (Folder 32.27)
  - Development Policy Committee — Board of Trustees, 1979-1980 (Folder 32.28)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee — Board of Trustees, 1979 (Folder 32.29)
  - Governance Committee — Board of Trustees, 1979-1980 (Folder 32.30)
  - Proposed Changes of the Governance, Apr 1980 (Folder 32.31)
  - Investments and Finance Committee — Board of Trustees, 1979-1980 (Folder 32.32)
  - Investor Responsibility Committee — Board of Trustees, 1979-1980 (Folder 32.33)
  - Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Trustees — Executive Committee, Oct 1979 (Folder 32.34)
  - Athletics Building Planning, 1977-1979 (Folder 32.35)
  - Physical Education Facility Outline Specifications and Building Description — Daniel F. Tully Associates, 1979 (Folder 32.36)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Dec 1979 (Folder 32.37)
  - Proposed Amendments to By-Laws of the Board of Trustees, Sept 1979 (Folder 32.38)
  - Amendments to By-Laws of the Board of Trustees Adopted, Oct 1979 (Folder 32.39)
  - Tributes to Jocelyn Breed, Bill Dietel, Jerry Pratt, and Don Wilson, May 1979 (Folder 32.40)
  - Barnes and Roache Report, Dec 1979 (Folder 33.1)
  - Cover Letter for Barnes and Roach Report, Dec 1979 (Folder 33.2)
  - Minutes of the Board of Trustees Meeting, Feb 1980 (Folder 33.3)
  - Statements on College Admissions and Recruitment and Collegiate Athletics, 1979 (Folder 33.4)
  - Proceedings Report of the Meeting of the Board of Trustees, Dec 1979 (Folder 33.5)
  - Proceedings Report of the Meeting of the Board of Trustees, Feb 1980 (Folder 33.6)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Feb 1980 (Folder 33.7)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Feb 1980 (Folder 33.8)
  - Major Agenda Items for May Board of Trustees Meeting, 1980 (Folder 33.9)
  - Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Trustees, Dec 1979 (Folder 33.10)
  - Minutes of the Meeting of the Board of Trustees — Executive Session, Dec 1979 (Folder 33.11)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, May 1980 (Folder 33.12)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1979-1980 (Folder 33.13)
  - Nominations Committee, 1979-1980 (Folder 33.14)
  - Committee on Structure and Functioning of the Trustees, 1980 (Folder 33.15)
  - Mobil Corporation — Correspondence on South Africa, 1979-1980 (Folder 33.16)
  - Ad hoc Priorities Committee — Board of Trustees, 1979-1980 (Folder 33.17)
  - South African Consulate General Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Folder 33.18)
  - South Africa — General Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Folder 33.19)
  - South Africa — General Correspondence, 1978 (Folder 33.20)
  - The Monthly Review — J. and W. Seligman and Co., 1980 (Folder 33.21)
  - Chaplaincy Review Committee Survey — Extra Copies, 1980 (Folder 33.22)
  - Governance Changes — Extra Copies, Mar 1981 (Folder 33.23)
  - Student Lists, 1983 (Folder 33.24)
  - Student Lists, 1981-1982 (Folder 33.25)
  - Student Lists, 1981-1983 (Folder 33.26)
  - Student Lists, 1980 (Folder 33.27)
  - Groundbreaking — Physical Education Building, 1981 (Folder 33.28)
  - Physical Education Building — Energy Concern, 1980 (Folder 33.29)
  - Athletics Facility (Priorities), 1978-1983 (Folder 33.30)
  - President’s Discretionary Funds, 1978-1980 (Folder 34.1)
  - President’s Discretionary Funds, 1977-1978 (Folder 34.2)
  - President’s Discretionary Funds, 1972-1977 (Folder 34.3)
  - Barnes and Roche, Inc., 1978-1979 (Folder 34.4)
  - Chemistry Building Facilities, 1979-1980 (Folder 34.5)
  - Barnes and Roche, Inc., 1979 (Folder 34.6)
  - Barnes and Roche, Inc. — Reports, 1978-1979 (Folder 34.7)
  - AAVC — Nelson Report, 1973-1976 (Folder 34.8)
  - Talks and Speeches, 1976-1981 (Folder 34.9)
  - Administrative Reorganization, 1979 (Folder 34.10)
  - Administrative Review Format, 1980 (Folder 34.11)
  - IBM Selectric Typewriter Magnetic Card (Folder 34.12)
  - Budget, 1979-1981 (Folder 34.13)
  - Conference Pamphlets — Correspondence and Notes (Folder 34.14)
  - President’s Funds and Gifts, 1979-1980 (Folder 34.15)
  - Receipts, 1980-1981 (Folder 34.16)
  - Administrative Retreat, 1979 (Folder 34.17)
  - Faculty Meetings — General and Dates, 1978-1980 (Folder 34.18)
  - Faculty Meeting, Nov 1979 (Folder 34.19)
  - Coeducation for Tomorrow Committee, 1978 (Folder 34.20)
  - College Council, 1980 (Folder 34.21)
  - Faculty Elections, 1979-1981 (Folder 34.22)
  - Committee on Admission, 1979-1981 (Folder 34.23)
  - Appeal Committee, 1979 (Folder 34.24)
  - Ad Hoc Committee to Study the Freshman Year and General Education at Vassar, 1979 (Folder 34.25)
  - Ad Hoc Advisory Committee on the Mellon Grant for Faculty Development, 1979 (Folder 34.26)
  - Committee on Sculpture, 1979 (Folder 34.27)
  - Faculty Appointment Review, 1979 (Folder 34.28)
  - Faculty Appointments and Contracts (Correspondence), 1979 (Folder 34.29)
  - Faculty Benefits, 1979 (Folder 34.30)
  - Faculty Candidates Interviews, 1981 (Folder 34.31)
  - Faculty Children Tuition Aid (Forms: Form File), 1971-1979 (Folder 34.32)
  - Faculty Compensation, 1980 (Folder 34.33)
  - Faculty and Course Evaluation, 1979-1981 (Folder 34.34)
  - Faculty Drop-in Hours, 1983 (Folder 34.35)
  - Faculty Housing, 1979-1981 (Folder 34.36)
  - Faculty Leaves, 1979 (Folder 34.37)
  - Faculty Salary Budget, 1980 (Folder 34.38)
  - Faculty Reviews, 1980 (Folder 34.39)
  - Faculty Reviews, 1979 (Folder 34.40)
  - Faculty Salary Scales, 1979-1980 (Folder 34.41)
  - Faculty Salary Scales, 1978-1979 (Folder 34.42)
  - Faculty Salary Study, 1981 (Folder 34.43)
  - Faculty Tenure, 1975 (Folder 34.44)
  - American Association of University Professors, 1978-1979 (Folder 34.45)
  - American Association of University Women, 1978-1979 (Folder 34.46)
  - Angelica Bell Dinner, 1980-1981 (Folder 34.47)
  - Friends of the Art Gallery, 1976-1979 (Folder 34.48)
  - Athletics Reports and Proposals, 1977-1979 (Folder 34.49)
  - Athletics, 1978-1979 (Folder 34.50)
  - Athletics (Other Colleges), 1976-1979 (Folder 34.51)
  - College Freshmen — National Norms, 1979-1980 (Folder 35.1)
  - Convocation, 1974-1977 (Folder 35.2)
  - Committee on Investor Responsibility — Campus, 1979-1981 (Folder 35.3)
  - Energy Conservation Committee, 1979-1980 (Folder 35.4)
  - Committee on Fellowships, 1979-1982 (Folder 35.5)
  - Committee on Governance, 1981 (Folder 35.6)
  - Judy Lewittes/Development, 1988-1989 (Folder 35.7)
  - Development, 1987-1988 (Folder 35.8)
  - Development, 1988-1989 (Folder 35.9)
  - Development Letters for President Fergusson (Folder 35.10)
  - Trustee Biographical Information (Folder 35.11)
  - AAVC Council — VBS to Speak, Oct 1983 (Folder 35.12)
  - AAVC Fall Council, 1983 (Folder 35.13)
  - Development Program for the 80s, 1986 (Folder 35.14)
  - Development, 1986 (Folder 35.15)
  - Completed Calls (President) (Folder 35.16)
  - Development Calls, 1986-1987 (Folder 35.17)
  - Development, 1987 (Folder 35.18)
  - Development #2, 1987 (Folder 35.19)
  - Development, 1987-1988 (Folder 35.20)
  - Development, 1987-1988 (Folder 36.1)
  - Trustee Budgets, 1978-1979 (Folder 36.2)
  - Institutional Memberships, 1978-1979 (Folder 36.3)
  - President’s Budgets, 1978-1979 (Folder 36.4)
  - Wellesley — Commission on the Future of the College, Mar 1971 (Folder 36.5)
  - 1976 Master Plan, Jan 1976 (Folder 36.6)
  - Amherst — Report on Long Range Planning, May 1971 (Folder 36.7)
  - Amherst — Report on College Size and Coeducation, Jan 1971 (Folder 36.8)
  - Yale — Report on Future of the College (Folder 36.9)
  - Report to the Curriculum Committee of the Vassar/Wesleyan Program, Jan 1980 (Folder 36.10)
  - Loose Reports, 1968, 1978 (Folder 36.11)
  - Haverford — Case Study-Evaluation Documents, 1972-1974 (Folder 36.12)
  - Colgate — Documents, 1971-1973 (Folder 36.13)
  - Princeton — Bressler Plan, Nov 1971 (Folder 36.14)
  - Oberlin — Education Commission, 1971 (Folder 36.15)
  - Search for Coordinator for Career Services and Field Work — Interviewee Folders, 1979-1980; (13 folders) (Folders 36.16-36.29)
  - Correspondence — Career Services, 1979-1980 (Folder 36.30)
  - Applicants — Career Services, 1979-1980 (Folder 36.31)
  - Search for Coordinator for Career Services and Field Work — Background Files, 1978-1979; (8 folders) (Folders 37.1-37.8)
  - The Regents 1976 Master Plan — New York State, 1973-1976 (Folder 37.9)
  - Development Office (Includes Contracts), 1981-1983 (Folder 37.10)
  - PepsiCo Foundation, 1982 (Folder 37.11)
  - 7-College Development Conference, 1982-1983 (Folder 37.12)
  - Judith A. Lewittes — Executive Director (Development), 1981-1984 (Folder 37.13)
  - National Council, 1983 (Folder 37.14)
  - National Council, 1980-1984 (Folder 37.15)
  - Carol G. Salguero — Director/Development, 1980-1982 (Folder 37.16)
  - Delma Vander Veer — Associate Director (Development), 1980-1983 (Folder 37.17)
  - Bernice Regunberg — Director AAVC Fund, 1982-1983 (Folder 37.18)
  - Academic Program Development, 1982-1985 (Folder 37.19)
  - C. Bunting, 1982-1985 (Folder 37.20)
  - E. Schalk, 1982-1985 (Folder 37.21)
  - Trustee, 1982-1985 (Folder 37.22)
  - Admission Candidates — To be Followed-Up, 1985 (Folder 37.23)
  - Recommendation Letters to Admissions Re Students (Confidential), 1984-1985 (Folder 37.24)
  - Admission/Inquiries and Complaints, 1980-1984 (Folder 37.25)
  - Office of Admissions, 1980-1984 (Folder 37.26)
  - Fred R. Brooks, Jr. — Director, 1980-1983 (Folder 37.27)
  - Ziva Dahl — Assistant Director, 1981-1983 (Folder 37.28)
  - Admissions Director, 1980 (Folder 37.29)
  - Natalie Marshall — Vice President, 1979-1985 (Folder 38.1)
  - Administrative Area, 1979-1983 (Folder 38.2)
  - Material on Employment, 1982-1983 (Folder 38.3)
  - Student Area, 1981-1983 (Folder 38.4)
  - David Eckwall — Director, 1983-1984 (Folder 38.5)
  - Peggy Streit — Director, 1980-1981 (Folder 38.6)
  - Office of Campus Activities, 1980-1984 (Folder 38.7)
  - Ronald T. Lambert — Executive Director, 1980-1984 (Folder 38.8)
  - H. Patrick Sullivan, 1980-1984 (Folder 38.9)
  - H. Patrick Sullivan, 1984-1985 (Folder 38.10)
  - Office of the Dean of the College, 1980-1985 (Folder 38.11)
  - H. Patrick Sullivan — Dean, 1980-1984 (Folder 38.12)
  - Contracts — HPS, 1982-1983 (Folder 38.13)
  - Contracts — HPS, 1980-1981 (Folder 38.14)
  - Patricia Kaurouma/Minority and Special Students, 1981-1982 (Folder 38.15)
  - Patricia Kaurouma — Revamp of Office of Advisor to Minority and Special Students, 1981 (Folder 38.16)
  - Independent Program — Anthony Wohl, Ch., 1978-1983 (Folder 38.17)
  - Chemical Bank Meeting, Jun 1985 (Folder 38.18)
  - Colton Johnson — Dean, 1981-1985 (Folder 38.19)
  - Office of the Dean of Studies, 1980-1985 (Folder 38.20)
  - Development Office, 1984-1985 (Folder 38.21)
  - National Development Council, 1984 (Folder 38.22)
  - Clemmie Peterson, Oct 1984 (Folder 38.23)
  - Office of Financial Aid (General), 1980-1985 (Folder 38.24)
  - Director of Financial Aid, 1980-1984 (Folder 38.25)
  - Office of Press and Information, 1979-1980 (Folder 38.26)
  - Press and Information Office, 1982-1985 (Folder 38.27)
  - Vassar Views, 1982-1984 (Folder 38.28)
  - Office of the Registrar, 1980-1985 (Folder 38.29)
  - Office of the Dean of Residence, 1981-1985 (Folder 38.30)
  - Donald Budd — Assistant Comptroller, 1980-1981 (Folder 38.31)
  - Vassar Press Releases, 1982-1985 (Folder 38.32)
  - Treasurer/Legal Fees, 1983 (Folder 38.33)
  - Facilities Financial Exposure, Dec 1, 1986 (Folder 38.34)
  - Treasurer and Chief Financial Officer, 1981-1985 (Folder 38.35)
  - Bursar, 1982-1985 (Folder 38.36)
  - Budget Committee, 1986-1987 (Folder 39.1)
  - Budget Committee Meetings (VBS), 1985-1986 (Folder 39.2)
  - Budget Committee Meeting (VBS), Feb 1986 (Folder 39.3)
  - Budget Committee Meeting (VBS), Jan 1986 (Folder 39.4)
  - Budget Committee Meeting (VBS), Dec 1985 (Folder 39.5)
  - Building and Grounds Committee, 1985-1987 (Folder 39.6)
  - President Smith, 1985 (Folder 39.7)
  - Development Committee, 1985-1987 (Folder 39.8)
  - Executive Committee Meeting (VBS), Summer 1984 (Folder 39.9)
  - Executive Committee Meeting (VBS), Dec 1985 (Folder 39.10)
  - Executive Committee, 1985-1986 (Folder 39.11)
  - Executive Committee, Sep 1985 (Folder 39.12)
  - Faculty and Studies Committee, 1986-1987 (Folder 39.13)
  - Forward Planning and Priorities Committee, 1985 (Folder 39.14)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1985-1986 (Folder 39.15)
  - Investments and Finance Committee Meeting, Nov 1987 (Folder 39.16)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, Jun 1987 (Folder 39.17)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, 1987 (Folder 39.18)
  - Report on Case Testing, Dec 1979 (Folder 39.19)
  - Investments and Finance — Reports and Loose Materials, 1985-1987 (Folder 39.20)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, Dec 1986 (Folder 39.21)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, Nov 1986 (Folder 39.22)
  - Investments and Finance Committee Meeting (VBS), May 1986 (Folder 39.23)
  - Investments and Finance Committee Meeting (VBS), Jan 1986 (Folder 39.24)
  - Investments and Finance Committee Meeting, Sep 1985 (Folder 39.25)
  - Investments and Finance Committee, Aug 1984 (Folder 39.26)
  - Investor Responsibility Committee, 1985-1987 (Folder 39.27)
  - Investments and Finance Committee Meeting (VBS), Dec 1985 (Folder 39.28)
  - J and W Seligman, 1985-1987 (Folder 39.29)
  - Joint Development Coordinating Committee, 1986 (Folder 39.30)
  - Recommendations on Development Activities, Sep 1987 (Folder 39.31)
  - Nominations Committee, 1986-1987 (Folder 39.32)
  - Nominations Committee, 1985-1987 (Folder 39.33)
  - Miles Lewis, 1984-1987 (Folder 39.34)
  - Management/Information System, Dec 1983 (Folder 39.35)
  - Trustee Meeting (FF), Feb 1987 (Folder 39.36)
  - Trustee Meetings — General, 1985-1988 (Folder 40.1)
  - Trustees — General, 1985-1987 (Folder 40.2)
  - Trustees Minutes (Extra Copies), 1985-1986 (Folder 40.3)
  - Chairman of the Board, 1986-1987 (Folder 40.4)
  - Trustees Addresses and Telephone Numbers, 1985-1986 (Folder 40.5)
  - V.C. Board of Trustees (VBS), Feb 1986 (Folder 40.6)
  - V.C. Board of Trustees Meeting (VBS), Oct 1985 (Folder 40.7)
  - Trustees Committee Assignments, 1985-1986 (Folder 40.8)
  - Elizabeth Villard, 1979-1986 (Folder 40.9)
  - Audit Committee, 1980 (Folder 40.10)
  - Budget Committee, 1986-1987 (Folder 40.11)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, Oct 1981 (Folder 40.12)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — Dixie Sheridan, Feb 1982 (Folder 40.13)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting, May 1982 (Folder 40.14)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — Dixie Sheridan, Oct 1982 (Folder 40.15)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — Dixie Sheridan, Dec 1982 (Folder 40.16)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — VBS, Oct 1985 (Folder 40.17)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — Pat Tyler, Oct 1985 (Folder 40.18)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — Norma Kelly, Oct 1985 (Folder 40.19)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — Robert Parks, Oct 1985; (1 folder) (Folder 40.20)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — VBS, Feb 1986 (Folder 40.21)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — Pat Tyler, Feb 1986 (Folder 40.22)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — Norma Kelly, Feb 1986 (Folder 40.23)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — Pat Tyler, May 1986 (Folder 40.24)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — Norma Kelly, May 1986 (Folder 40.25)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — Pat Tyler, Oct 1986 (Folder 40.26)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — Fran Fergusson, May 1987 (Folder 40.27)
  - Board of Trustees Meeting — Loose Materials, 1984-1985 (Folder 40.28)
  - Ahern, John, 1981-1987 (Folder 40.29)
  - Albers, Henry, 1978-1989 (Folder 40.30)
  - Appenzellar, Jean M., 1968-1985 (Folder 40.31)
  - Arlyck, Elizabeth C., 1978-1982 (Folder 40.32)
  - Armstrong, James, 1984-1989 (Folder 40.33)
  - Askew, Pamela, 1974-1988 (Folder 40.34)
  - Badanes, Jerome, 1985-1987 (Folder 40.35)
  - Bartlett, Lynn C., 1963-1987 (Folder 40.36)
  - Bean, Noel Jay, 1979-1985 (Folder 40.37)
  - Beck, Curt W., 1963-1989 (Folder 40.38)
  - Becker, Richard, 1980-1989 (Folder 40.39)
  - Bergon, Frank A., 1972-1985 (Folder 40.40)
  - Bickerstaff, Joyce, 1989 (Folder 40.41)
  - Born, Richard J., 1976-1984 (Folder 40.42)
  - Briggs, Charles L., 1980-1985 (Folder 40.43)
  - Brisman, Susan H., 1974-1985 (Folder 40.44)
  - Broude, Gwen J., 1976-1984 (Folder 40.45)
  - Brown, David H., 1978-1984 (Folder 40.46)
  - Bunnell, Frederick P., 1967-1985 (Folder 40.47)
  - Campbell, Kathy Ann, 1978-1984 (Folder 40.48)
  - Carroll, Eugene, 1967-1989 (Folder 40.49)
  - Challey, James F., 1973-1982 (Folder 40.50)
  - Chaplin III, Arthur D., 1979-1982 (Folder 40.51)
  - Chandler, Kenneth A., 1965-1985 (Folder 40.52)
  - Charlap, Peter, 1979-1985 (Folder 40.53)
  - Chin, Yin-Lien C., 1967-1985 (Folder 40.54)
  - Christensen, Carol A., 1973-1986 (Folder 41.1)
  - Chromey, Frederick R., 1988 (Folder 41.2)
  - Clark, Jonathan C., 1973-1989 (Folder 41.3)
  - Clark, Judy, 1983-1989 (Folder 41.4)
  - Cohen, Colleen B., 1980-1984 (Folder 41.5)
  - Cohen, Miriam J., 1977-1985 (Folder 41.6)
  - Constantinople, Anne, 1984-1986 (Folder 41.7)
  - Cook, Ray, 1982 (Folder 41.8)
  - Coyle, Beverly, 1977-1984 (Folder 41.9)
  - Crow, Todd William, 1969-1985 (Folder 41.10)
  - Czula, Roman, 1975-1986 (Folder 41.11)
  - Daniels, Elizabeth A., 1964-1989 (Folder 41.12)
  - Darlington, Beth Mary, 1967-1988 (Folder 41.13)
  - Day, James H., 1970-1982 (Folder 41.14)
  - Degilio, John F., 1971-1982 (Folder 41.15)
  - Deiters, Sister Joan A., 1979-1985 (Folder 41.16)
  - Demarco, Nicholas S., 1966-1982 (Folder 41.17)
  - Demaria, Robert, 1975-1984 (Folder 41.18)
  - Duffy, Michael, 1984-1988 (Folder 41.19)
  - Fabozzi, Patricia A., 1982-1983 (Folder 41.20)
  - Fairservis (Jr.), Walter A., 1969-1984 (Folder 41.21)
  - Farganis, James, 1978-1988 (Folder 41.22)
  - Farganis, Sondra Joyce, 1970-1988 (Folder 41.23)
  - Ferdinand, Joseph J., 1976-1981 (Folder 41.24)
  - Feroe, John Albert, 1974-1988 (Folder 41.25)
  - Flad, Harvey Keyes, 1972-1984 (Folder 41.26)
  - Fortuna, Robert, 1963-1982 (Folder 41.27)
  - Fritz, Robert S., 1985-1986 (Folder 41.28)
  - Gallagher, Merellyn, 1969-1980 (Folder 41.29)
  - Gardia-Renart, Louis, 1964-1984 (Folder 41.30)
  - Gesek, Thaddeus Joseph, 1959-1989 (Folder 41.31)
  - Gifford, William W., 1966-1984 (Folder 41.32)
  - Gillin, Donald G., 1968-1985 (Folder 41.33)
  - Glasse, John H., 1969-1988 (Folder 41.34)
  - Goldensohn, Lorrie, 1985 (Folder 41.35)
  - Goldsiein, Judith L., 1977-1983 (Folder 41.36)
  - Gounaris, Anne D., 1966-1985 (Folder 41.37)
  - Gray, Obika, 1983 (Folder 41.38)
  - Green, Sondra (Mrs. Howard), 1964-1982 (Folder 41.39)
  - Greenwood, Marci, 1977-1989 (Folder 41.40)
  - Gregg, Richard, 1969-1984 (Folder 41.41)
  - Grennan, Eamon, 1974-1985 (Folder 41.42)
  - Griffen, Clyde, 1959-1990 (Folder 41.43)
  - Hammond, Christina Noring (Mrs. William A.), 1961-1980 (Folder 41.44)
  - Havelock, Christine Mitchell, 1964-1986 (Folder 41.45)
  - Hemmes, Richard, 1972-1983 (Folder 41.46)
  - Herbst, Lawrence A., 1970-1986 (Folder 41.47)
  - Hodges, Norman Edward, 1969-1984 (Folder 41.48)
  - Huenink, Peter G., 1975-1984 (Folder 41.49)
  - Hunter, Mary-Alice, 1960-1980 (Folder 41.50)
  - Hytier, Adrienne D., 1959-1980 (Folder 41.51)
  - Imbrie, Ann, 1979-1985 (Folder 41.52)
  - Jehle, Geoffrey, 1986-1988 (Folder 41.53)
  - Jenning, Andrew, 1982-1983 (Folder 41.54)
  - Johnson, C. Colton, 1965-1986 (Folder 41.55)
  - Johnsen, John H., 1965-1985 (Folder 41.56)
  - Johnson, Glen, 1964-1986 (Folder 41.57)
  - Johnson, Jeh Vincent, 1964-1981 (Folder 41.58)
  - Johnson, Lucille Lewis, 1973-1989 (Folder 42.1)
  - Johnson, Patricia R., 1964-1989 (Folder 42.2)
  - Johnson, Shirley B., 1967-1984 (Folder 42.3)
  - Kalin, Jesse G., 1971-1989 (Folder 42.4)
  - Katz, Majorie Fink, 1973-1979 (Folder 42.5)
  - Kava, Ruth A., 1984 (Folder 42.6)
  - Kempton, Daniel R., 1980-1985 (Folder 42.7)
  - Kennett, David Anthony, 1976-1989 (Folder 42.8)
  - Kenworthy, Patricia, 1976-1984 (Folder 42.9)
  - Kerr, Cynthia Boardman, 1976-1985 (Folder 42.10)
  - Klabes, Gunter, 1974-1985 (Folder 42.11)
  - Klimoff, Alexis, 1971-1988 (Folder 42.12)
  - Kohl, Benjamin, 1966-1990 (Folder 42.13)
  - Krueger, Janet T., 1979-1983 (Folder 42.14)
  - Kuretsky, Susan Donahue, 1975-1986; (1 folder) (Folder 42.15)
  - Le Clezio, Marguerite, 1980-1987 (Folder 42.16)
  - Leonard, Eileen B., 1975-1985 (Folder 42.17)
  - Liang, His Huey, 1964-1990 (Folder 42.18)